eupse.co 2016-04-24

# 411NUM

**Who we are**

411num – is a service that aggregates information publicly available online and helps you to find other people and connect with them.

411num searches the web in real-time for publicly available data linked to names, just in the same manner as Google, Bing or any other web search engine processes general queries.

This document describes how we treat your personal data and other information about you. If you are looking for the guidance on how to log in to 411num, or wondering what the general rules and restrictions when using this website are, please take a look at our [Terms of Use](http://411num.com/terms-of-service).

By accessing this website you agree and acknowledge to be bound by this Privacy Policy in its entirety.

**Glossary**

  * Website – this web site.
  * 411num/We – the administration of the Website.
  * User/You – person using the Website at least 18 years old, legally capable to enter agreements. If you are using the Website on behalf of any legal entity (company), you must have the authority to enter agreements on behalf of the company.
  * Personal Data - information or its combination that can be used to identify the User as an individual, such as, for example name, email address, phone number, home address.
  * Non-Personally Identifiable Information – information about an individual that alone or in combination with similar information can not be used to identify the User, for example, address alone, or computer’s domain name and IP address. 
  * Information – any Personal Data, Non-Personally Identifiable Information and/or any other information that is public by default.
  * Search results Page – aggregates information and hyperlinks related to a search query that combines any first and last name (ex. «John» + «Doe»). The Search results’ Page may refer to multiple entries.
  * User page, Your page – contains the Profile of the particular person. (ex. John M. Doe; (111) 222 3333; 1 Main Str., Small City, 20005, Major Country).

**Information Indexed by 411num**

We do not mine for any personal data. We aggregate or index and provide links to the information:

  * that is already in free access;
  * has been made available by you or with your consent;
  * openly circulates on the Internet.

You might find information about yourself on the Website. It means that it has been published or released on the Internet by you or with your consent earlier, and 411num is not the source of such publication or release.

Most of the information that goes through the Website is not stored, collected or otherwise processed by 411num. We work like a search engine that does not generate or produce its own content, information or data. Information found on Search results Pages is the example of such indexing of content and information available on the Internet and connecting various pieces of information.

At the same time we might collect and store some information, for example to make User pages available as a part of the Website. In case it contains Personal Data we protect it in the same manner we treat Personal Data provided by you directly (please, see Section “Information Provided by Users” further below).

**Information Provided by Users**

You can provide Personal Data to us at the moment of registration or while filling in your Profile.

Usually this Personal Data narrows down to:

  * first, middle and last name;
  * home address;
  * home phone number.

This list is tentative and may vary and/or be extended depending on the Website’s future developments and upgrades.

**_When you use the Website, you are consenting to the collection, transfer, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information, including Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy._**

The purpose of processing your Personal Data is to facilitate the completeness and accuracy of people’s search worldwide and to expedite the process of connecting people on the Internet. The Website is designed to help you and other people to share information with others.

We warrant that:

  * We will not sell or rent your Personal Data to a third party, or otherwise use it out of accordance with the purpose of processing your Personal Data;
  * We will take commercially reasonable precautions to protect your Personal Data from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. We store all information using industry-standard techniques. We do not guarantee or warrant that such techniques will prevent unauthorized access to information that we store;
  * We will not use or disclose Personal Data except:
    * as necessary to run the Website according to the purpose of processing your Personal Data and the Website’s performance;
    * as required by any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request;
    * as necessary to enforce the Terms of Use
    * to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues;
    * as necessary to protect the rights, safety, or property of 411num, Users, or any other third parties;
    * in other ways described in this Privacy Policy, Terms of Use or to which you have otherwise consented;
  * We will only retain Personal Data as long as necessary for the fulfillment of the purpose of processing your Personal Data.

You understand that by publishing any information in your Profile you make it publicly available on the Internet.

If you would like to remove your information, including Personal Data from User Page, please review Section “Removing your Information” of our [Terms of Use](http://411num.com/terms-of-service#remove_your_information).

**Other Information Collected Automatically**

We automatically receive and record information from your web browser when you interact with the Website, including your IP address and cookie information. This information is used for fighting spam/malware and also to facilitate collection of data concerning your interaction with the Website (for example what links you have clicked on).

Generally, the Website automatically collects usage information, such as the number and frequency of visitors to the Website. We may use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, but not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us and third parties authorized by us to figure out how often individuals use parts of the Website so that we can analyze and improve them.

**Cookies**

Cookies are pieces of text that may be provided to your computer through your web browser when you access a website. Your browser stores cookies in a manner associated with each website you visit. We use cookies to enable the Website to recognize your web browser and tell us how and when you visit the Website and otherwise use it through the Internet.

Our cookies do not, by themselves, contain Personal Data, and we do not combine the general information collected through cookies with other Personal Data to tell us who you are. As noted, however, we do use cookies to identify that your web browser has accessed aspects of the Website and may associate that information with your account if you have one.

This Privacy Policy covers our use of cookies only and does not cover the use of cookies by third parties. We do not control when or how third parties place cookies on your computer. For example, third party websites to which a link points may set cookies on your computer. Also the following third party services use cookies on the Website (examples): Google Analytics, Facebook Like Button, Twitter Follow button, Google +1 button and some others. Some of these services may be used to track your behavior on other websites and we have no control over this.

**Advertisements**

To support and enhance the Website, we may serve advertisements, and also allow third parties advertisements, through the Website. These advertisements are sometimes targeted and served to particular Users and may come from third party companies: ad networks, online advertising platforms (ex. Google AdSense).

Advertisements served through the Website may be targeted to Users who fit a certain general profile category and may be based on your activity on third parties’ websites and services.

These third-party ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Website. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content.

We do not provide Personal Data to any ad networks or online advertising platforms for use outside of the Website.

**Information we do not process or collect**

We do not currently collect:

  * Financial information;
  * Account information, such as your email address, username and password. That information is collected and stored by Facebook, a third party service provider, which processes and stores that information. Please, review Facebook applicable terms of service and privacy policy if needed. We will collect and store only your Facebook user ID;
  * Any information concerning children. We do not knowingly collect or solicit information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to use the Website. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we take immediate steps to remove that information;
  * Any sensitive Personal Data. We do not deal with any sensitive information, such as related to the racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious beliefs, physical or mental health or condition, crime or court records, etc.

**Miscellaneous**

411num operations are not primarily located in the European Union. If you provide information to us, the information will be transferred out of the European Union (EU). By providing Personal Data to us, you are consenting to its storage and use as described in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy does not govern the collection and use of information by any other third party. If you follow a link that is located on the Website, make sure you have reviewed carefully the third party’s website privacy policy and/or terms of services.

We store information on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time at our sole discretion. The most current version will always be located here <http://411num.com/privacy-policy>. By continuing to access or use the Website after the revisions become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please send them using [Contact Us](http://411num.com/contacts) form.

Effective: January 5, 2013 Last updated: January 5, 2013
